What I didn't realize about this song,
it's like a 2000 era R&B song where it
has the rapper [music] and the singer,
but he's doing both parts. If you listen
to the first verse of this song, he's
singing in a super high falsetto voice.
Like that's the woman's part.
>> And then his second verse is the ja rule
part where first verse was Ashanti.
>> I be in the summer when I'm ready to
drift. My Ferrari handle [music] better.
cliche 2000's rap verse where the guy is
on the R&B song, so he kind of wants to
be smooth. He's dynamic enough. He goes
super low for the rap verse and he's
singing midtone for the hook and he's
singing falsetto for the the
quoteunquote woman part.
>> And his falsetto sounds good on this.
>> Yeah, whatever key this is. I didn't
look it up, but like this is a great key
for him. Suits his voice really well. It
suits it perfectly.
[music]